thanks for joining us in this webinar on
感谢您加入我们在此网络研讨会中
Java 12 today so before I start I'll
今天的Java 12，所以在我开始之前
address the main question why should you
解决主要问题你为什么要
attend the session and why you need to
参加会议以及为什么需要
know what's new in Java 12 so if you can
了解Java 12的新功能，如果可以的话
identify yourself in one of these
在其中之一中识别自己
situations I think you are a good fit
我认为你很适合
for the session so the first one is this
在会议上，所以第一个是这个
the session title came as a surprise to
会议标题使
you and maybe you thought really Java 12
您，也许您认为真的是Java 12
is already out and here's the second one
已经出来了，这是第二个
you know Java 12 is out and you are
你知道Java 12已经发布了
curious to find out what's in it another
好奇地发现里面有什么
situation maybe since you program in
情况可能是因为您在
Java everyone around you expects you to
Java您周围的每个人都希望您能够
know what's new in Java 12 but since you
知道Java 12的新功能，但是自从您
are programming in an older version of
正在使用旧版本的
Java you didn't really get the time to
Java，您实际上没有时间
explore the latest version and here's
探索最新版本，这里是
one more perhaps people come to you and
也许有人来找你，
seek your advice on whether they should
就他们是否应该征询您的意见
move to Java 12 or not so if you think
迁移到Java 12还是不迁移到Java 12
you could see yourself in one of these
您可以在其中之一中看到自己
situations or perhaps a similar one you
情况或类似的情况
are in the right place so okay so this
在正确的地方，这样就可以了
was about typing yes in the chat window
关于在聊天窗口中输入是
if you think you could see yourself in
如果您认为自己可以看到自己
any of the previous situations or a
以前的任何情况或
similar one just so you know that yes
类似，只是您知道
you are attending the right session okay
你参加正确的会议好吗
so here's the agenda for today's session
所以这是今天会议的议程
so we are saying hello to Java 12 so
所以我们对Java 12表示欢迎
I'll cover the impact of the release
我将介绍发布的影响
guidance on the adoption of Java 12 I'll
我将通过Java 12的指南
take you through the links where you can
带您通过链接进行操作
access the list of the changes in Java
访问Java中的更改列表
12 since it's a JetBrains webinar I will
12，因为这是JetBrains网络研讨会，我将
not cover each and every change which is
不能涵盖每一个变化
there in Java
在Java中
well I limit it to some of the changes
好吧，我将其限制为某些更改
and Java trial includes multiple small
Java试用包括多个小
changes and I've included a list
变化，我已经列出了清单
deliberately because these links will
故意因为这些链接将
help you find how you can perhaps
帮助您找到可能的方式
discover the exhaustive list of changes
发现详尽的变更清单
in Java 12 I'll take you through the
在Java 12中，我将带您完成
language changes in Java 12 which is the
Java 12中的语言变化是
new switch expressions alka also cover
新的开关表达式alka也涵盖了
how to move around the API changes again
如何再次遍历API更改
that's a list and not really of each and
那是一个列表，并不是每个列表的真正含义
every API which has changed in Java 12
Java 12中每个已更改的API
quickly I'll take you through the GC
很快，我会带您通过GC
changes we have a new GC and two major
变化，我们有一个新的GC和两个主要
modifications to the existing Jeevan GC
对现有Jeevan GC的修改
which is the garbage first collector
这是垃圾第一收集器
will also talk about whether you should
也将讨论您是否应该
be moving to Java 12 and at the end as
迁移到Java 12，最后以
Trisha said will conclude with questions
特丽莎（Trisha）说会以问题结尾
and answers so Oracle introduced the six
和答案，因此Oracle介绍了六个
months release cadence with Java 9 so
Java 9个月发布节奏
essentially all versions after Java 9
Java 9之后的所有版本
are released every 6 months and with the
每6个月发布一次，
six months release cadence a Java
六个月发布节奏Java
version is either a long term support
版本是长期支持
release or a short-term support release
发布或短期支持发布
so I ran a poll yesterday requesting
所以我昨天进行了一项民意调查
developers to share their experience
开发人员分享经验
with Java 12 a very high percentage
Java 12的百分比很高
which is 38% of people were really not
这是38％的人不是
aware the Java 12 is out and yes for
知道Java 12已经发布，是的
your information it was released on
您发布的信息
March 19th
3月19日
this year another high percentage of
今年的另一高百分比
people wanted to know what's new in it
人们想知道其中的新内容
and as we would expect
正如我们所期望的
very few are planning to move to Java 12
极少数计划迁移到Java 12
and also doubtful whether they should do
也怀疑他们是否应该这样做
so the least votes are where developers
所以最少的票是开发商
are curious to know that the Java 12
很好奇Java 12
works with other frameworks
与其他框架一起工作
or Jules also the newer versions are not
或者Jules也不是较新的版本
released with a hot lot of hype now the
现在发布了很多炒作
way they were released earlier when
他们早些时候被释放的方式
Oracle had the regular three years
甲骨文有定期的三年
release cadence so which explains why
释放节奏，这解释了为什么
people don't know when a new version is
人们不知道什么时候有新版本
released so here's another poll which
发布，所以这是另一个民意调查
reflects number one on the previous poll
反映上一次民意调查的第一名
why people are not aware about the new
为什么人们不了解新
releases the new releases of Java and
发行新版本的Java和
number two on Java's release cadence how
在Java的发布节奏上排名第二
it is affecting the adoption of newer
它影响更新的采用
versions because there are numerous
版本，因为有很多
polls to suggest that majority of
民意调查显示大多数
production code is still on Java 8 and
生产代码仍在Java 8和
we all agree with that
我们都同意这一点
but however that doesn't stop the
但这并不能阻止
developers from trying out the newer
开发人员尝试新产品
versions Java 9 was released in 2017
Java 9的版本于2017年发布
three years after Java 8 and its
Java 8及其之后的三年
adoption rate was slow because we had
采用率很慢，因为我们有
the module system which was kind of a
模块系统
showstopper in when we are talking about
当我们在谈论时
adoption of Java 9 also it was a show a
Java 9的采用也是一个展示
short-term support release Java 11 which
短期支持发布Java 11
was released last year September is a
去年9月发行的是
long-term support release and
长期支持发布和
organizations prefer to migrate from one
组织倾向于从一个迁移
LTS version to another
LTS版本到另一个
LTS version so the last version before
LTS版本，因此之前的最新版本
Java 11 was Java 8 so people are moving
Java 11是Java 8，因此人们不断前进
to Java 11 rather than moving to Java 12
迁移到Java 11而不是迁移到Java 12
so with the new release cadence of Java
因此，随着Java的新发行节奏
the rate of innovation is same because
创新率是相同的，因为
we are talking about releasing of the
我们正在谈论释放
features that could be used by
可以使用的功能
developers so Oracle is working on an
开发人员，因此Oracle正在开发
arm in the same pace what has changed is
步调一致，改变的是
the rate of delivery now every six
现在每六个交货率
months the developers get
开发人员获得的几个月
to work with the newer features of newer
使用较新的功能
features that come in Java of course we
Java当然具有的功能
also talked about the predictable dates
还谈到了可预测的日期
now we don't have to wait for a feature
现在我们不必等待功能
a star feature to complete to get a
完成一项明星功能
newer version of Java we know that every
我们知道Java的更新版本
six months we will get a new version
六个月后，我们将获得一个新版本
whether or not a feature is able to make
功能是否能够
it to a particular Java version not not
它不是特定的Java版本
so the features are not given that much
所以功能没有那么多
of importance as they were earlier given
像以前一样重要
and of course the new features are not
当然新功能不是
punished for being in time so has anyone
因及时而受到惩罚
of you been at at an event where if the
你们中的一个人
chief guest doesn't arrives in time
首席客人没有及时到达
all the rest of the people who are
所有其余的人
actually been there in time are punished
实际去过那里都受到惩罚
for being in time so that's how the Java
因为及时，所以这就是Java
release cadence is working now the
发行节奏现在正在工作
features which are ready they are
准备好了的功能
released with the next Java version and
与下一个Java版本一起发布，并且
the ones which are not the Java versions
不是Java版本的
are not delayed for those features so we
这些功能不会延迟，因此我们
get to the next one on on today's
进入今天的下一个
session they are on the agenda which is
会议，他们在议程上是
how to access what's new in Java 12 so
如何访问Java 12中的新功能
if you go to the link which is mentioned
如果您转到提到的链接
here I could just open this one and we
在这里，我可以打开这个，我们
would see the list of the G EPS which
会看到G EPS的列表
are included in Java 12 as you can see
如您所见，它包含在Java 12中
we have the features list here and so we
我们在这里有功能列表，所以我们
could see we could access what's new in
可以看到我们可以访问新功能
Java 12 using multiple ways
Java 12使用多种方式
I could access the GE PS which is the
我可以访问GE PS
jdk enhancement proposals which are the
jdk增强建议是
features that went in Java 12 and I
Java 12和我所拥有的功能
could also access the complete list of
也可以访问的完整列表
API changes which are included in Java
Java中包含的API更改
so this link is usually not accessible
因此通常无法访问此链接
by a lot of developers because a lot of
由很多开发人员提供，因为很多
developers don't know about this list so
开发人员对此列表一无所知
this one would give you the API
这个会给你API
differences between Java s 11 in Java SE
Java SE中Java s 11之间的区别
2 l so as you can see the changes are in
2升，如您所见
red font the additions are highlighted
红色字体突出显示添加项
with a green background and the removals
绿色背景和清除
are with a pink background so let's
是粉红色的背景，让我们
click this link here and we can actually
单击此链接，我们实际上可以
access what's happening in the Java API
访问Java API中发生的事情
so let's scroll to our favorite Java dot
让我们滚动到我们最喜欢的Java点
Lang and you can see and let's go to
郎，你可以看到，然后去
class string here's the class string and
类字符串，这是类字符串，
we can see there's one modification for
我们可以看到有一个修改
additions and in total there are five
增加，总共有五个
changes so let's click on Java string so
变化，让我们点击Java字符串
the additions as we saw earlier in the
正如我们前面所看到的
previous window the additions are
以前的窗口中添加的是
highlighted with a green background and
以绿色背景突出显示，并
in the left pane you could also scroll
在左窗格中，您也可以滚动
down again to find out what the
再次下来找出什么
additions are so described constable is
如此描述的稳定是
one of the methods which is new to Java
Java的新方法之一
which is new to class string in Java 12
Java 12中类字符串的新功能
you have in method indent and others as
你有方法缩进和其他
well so this link would give you a list
好吧，这个链接会给你一个列表
of all the additions modifications
所有附加修改中
deletions to Java
Java删除
ac-12 ok now let's go to the new
ac-12好的，现在让我们开始吧
language features in Java 12 so
Java 12中的语言功能
essentially we have only one which is
本质上我们只有一个
the switch expressions so
开关表达式如此
I'll move to the demo now so okay so
我现在去演示，好吧
we'll switch expressions we have an
我们将切换表达式，我们有一个
option of using the switch statements as
使用switch语句作为
switch expressions and as we know switch
开关表达式和我们所知道的开关
expressions are something an expression
表达是表达
is something which would return a value
是会返回值的东西
back to you and with Java 12 we could
回到您的手中，使用Java 12，我们可以
use a switch statement as both as an
使用switch语句作为
expression and as in statement so let's
表达式和声明中一样，让我们
start with some code here let me define
从这里的一些代码开始，让我定义
an enum which is single-use plastic and
一个用过的塑料枚举，
I create a couple of constants here and
我在这里创建了两个常数
the constants are spoon I have straw
常数是勺子，我有稻草
I have bottle and a cup and let me
我有酒杯和杯子让我
create a method which returns a value of
创建一个返回值为的方法
type and I say damage so this is kind of
类型，我说是损坏，所以这有点
trying to calculate the damage that you
试图计算您的伤害
are doing to your planet by using
通过使用对你的星球做
single-use plastic items okay so I pass
一次性塑料制品好吧，我通过了
in a value of method parameter of type
在类型的方法参数的值中
single-use plastic to this method and
一次性使用塑料的方法和
okay I have local variable here which I
好吧，我在这里有局部变量
return from this method and let me
从这种方法返回让我
switch on the method parameter and I say
打开方法参数，我说
if the case is spoon the damage which is
如果是汤匙的话
done to the environment is let's say 10
对环境做的比方说10
points I have a break state
点我有休息状态
Minn so that the control doesn't fall
Minn，以便控件不会掉落
through the case labels the second case
通过案例标签第二种情况
label is straw I say the damage in this
标签是稻草我说这是损害
case is 11 points again I used the break
案例又是11分我用了休息时间
statement for the next case label which
下一个案例标签的说明
is bottle let me say that the damage is
是瓶子，我要说的是
20 points so folks if you are using
大家20分，如果您正在使用
single-use plastic bottles in the damage
一次性塑料瓶中的损坏
is I think the most okay so we have
我认为最可以吗？
another break statement and last case
另一个中断声明和最后一个案例
label which is the top and now the
标签是顶部，现在是
damage is again 11 points okay so let me
伤害还是11点还可以，所以让我
reformat all the code using a shortcut
使用快捷方式重新格式化所有代码
which is control alt L so as you can see
如您所见，它是控制Alt L
the code looks much better with the
该代码看起来更好
formatting now okay so what can we do
现在格式化好了，我们该怎么办
okay so before I move further I would
好吧，在我继续之前，我会
like to state the project settings that
想说明项目设置
you must have in your IntelliJ IDEA so
您必须在IntelliJ IDEA中包含
that you can use the JDK 12 features so
您可以使用JDK 12功能
we can use ctrl alt shift to open the
我们可以使用ctrl alt shift打开
project structure and I already have my
项目结构，我已经有了我的
project settings as to well but if you
项目设置也不错，但是如果你
have it for a previous version then
然后将其用于先前版本
you'll have to change it to 12 and also
您必须将其更改为12
excuse me the project language level to
请问项目语言水平
12 so as you can see there are multiple
12，如您所见，有多个
options which are available so I could
可用的选项，所以我可以
have my project SDK at a particular
在特定的地方有我的项目SDK
number let's say 2 well but it's the
数字让我们说2好，但这是
language level that I use for my
我用于我的语言水平
IntelliJ IDEA project is
IntelliJ IDEA项目是
let's say ten I could actually compile
假设我实际上可以编译十个
my project to a previous version so I
我的项目到以前的版本，所以我
would have it as to well because I want
会很好，因为我想要
to use the switch expressions in Java 12
在Java 12中使用switch表达式
and of course if you don't have this you
当然，如果您没有这个
could go to project SDK create add a new
可以去项目SDK创建添加一个新的
SDK and since I already have J to get to
SDK，因为我已经有J了
L on my system so this I could use it
L在我的系统上，因此我可以使用它
but if you don't already have judicata
但如果您还没有judicata
valve on your system then probably you
在您的系统上安装阀门
would need to download and install it
需要下载并安装它
first and then go to the project
首先，然后去项目
structure settings and add it to your
结构设置并将其添加到您的
IntelliJ IDEA settings so that you can
IntelliJ IDEA设置，以便您可以
use it before you move forward okay so I
在继续前进之前使用它，好吧，我
click on ok so the settings are good and
单击确定，所以设置很好，
I click on OK so as you can see this
我单击确定，这样您就可以看到
switch statement which is the
switch语句是
traditional switch statement is a kind
传统的switch语句是一种
of multiple if-else statement I am
我是多个if-else语句
switching on the method parameter and
打开方法参数并
depending on the case I am assigning a
根据情况，我要分配一个
value to a variable so let's say how I
值给一个变量，让我们说说我如何
could convert that the switch statement
可以转换switch语句
to a switch expression so if I press alt
到一个开关表达式，所以如果我按alt
enter on the switch keyword I could use
输入我可以使用的switch关键字
the option of replacing with switch
用开关替换的选项
expression now isn't that so concise
现在的表达不是那么简洁
because I let me go back to the code
因为我让我回到代码
that I had earlier Wow so I'm going I'm
我以前有哇，所以我要走了
letting go so many lines of code again I
让我再放很多行代码
would press alt enter and replace with
将按alt输入并替换为
switch X use the option of replacing
开关X使用替换选项
with switch expression and this is what
与开关表达式，这是什么
I get again I can see that lemon is
我再一次看到柠檬是
underlined so let me see what IntelliJ
带下划线的，让我看看IntelliJ是什么
IDEA suggests here so it says I could
IDEA建议在这里说，我可以
merge the case cup with
与合并杯子
straw because because it is returning
稻草，因为因为它回来了
the same value so let me do that now
相同的价值，让我现在就做
let's compare this with the switch
让我们将其与开关进行比较
statement that we have earlier with the
我们之前拥有的声明
earlier switch statements it's not
之前的switch语句不是
possible to use multiple case labels in
可以在多个案例标签中使用
the same switch branch and with the
相同的开关分支和
previous statement I had I would have to
以前的陈述我不得不
use this on separate in separate
分开使用
branches but now with the switch
分支，但现在有了开关
expressions I could use it in the same
表达式我可以用在同一
branch of course the syntax is concise
语法当然是简洁的
you define what you have to return on
您定义必须返回的内容
the right side of the arrow key of the
箭头键的右侧
array of the arrow now let's see if I
箭头阵列现在让我们看看是否
could inline the variable so as you can
可以内联变量，以便您可以
notice at present this this code block
目前注意此代码块
is just assigning a value to the switch
只是给开关分配一个值
expression is assigning a value to the
表达式将值分配给
variable damage and just returning it so
可变的损害，只是退还所以
what we could do by inlining the
我们可以通过内联
variable is we could go we could do away
可变的是我们可以走，我们可以走
with the local variable damage and just
受到局部变量的损害
use the switch expression to return the
使用switch表达式返回
value wow this works like a charm now
价值哇，这就像现在的魅力
okay so we talked about making the
好吧，所以我们谈到了
switch statements concise we talked
切换语句简明扼要
about using multiple constants multiple
关于使用多个常量
case labels in a single branch we talked
我们讨论过的单个分支中的案例标签
about in lining the variable so let's
关于衬里变量，所以让我们
talk about the default false show so
谈论默认的假秀，所以
let's go back to the original code I
让我们回到原始代码
just use ctrl Z to go back to this one
只需使用Ctrl Z即可返回到此
so what happens if I just remove the
所以，如果我只是删除
break statement here in this case if I
如果我在这种情况下在这里中断声明
pass the value straw to the
将价值秸秆传递给
method the control will fall through
控件将失败的方法
case label straw to bottle and a value
案例标签秸秆到瓶子和价值
of 20 would be assigned to bottle but
20个将分配给瓶子，但
not if you use switch expressions so
如果您使用开关表达式，则不会
that's another advantage of using switch
那是使用开关的另一个优势
expressions and we also talked about the
表达式，我们还谈到了
exhaustive cases okay
详尽的案例还可以
let's again replace that with switch
让我们再次用switch替换它
expression and I in line this variable
表达式，我在此变量中
now what happens if I delete this value
现在，如果我删除此值会发生什么
so IntelliJ IDEA tells me that switch
所以IntelliJ IDEA告诉我该开关
expression does not cover all the
表达式不能涵盖所有
positive all the possible input values
正所有可能的输入值
because we are talking about an enum
因为我们在谈论一个枚举
here we have full constants for the enum
这里我们有完整的枚举常量
which could be passed to this method and
可以传递给此方法，
if I'm not governing one of the
如果我不管理其中之一
constants I have two options here so let
常量我在这里有两个选择，所以让
me see what are the options I could
我看看我有什么选择
either create a missing branch switch
要么创建丢失的分支交换机
branch which is bottle or I could insert
分支是瓶或我可以插入
a default branch so let me insert a
默认分支，所以让我插入一个
default branch here okay so this that's
默认分支在这里，所以这是
the default code of course I could
我当然可以使用默认代码
change it to what I want so what happens
将其更改为我想要的，这样会发生什么
okay so let me try out the other option
好吧，让我尝试其他选择
and now I choose creating a missing
现在我选择创造一个失踪者
switch branch visit which is bottle
切换分支访问是瓶
again I could define the value that I
再次，我可以定义我的价值
want now this is an enum where we know
现在想要这是一个我们知道的枚举
what are the possible values that could
有哪些可能的价值
be passed to the variable but what
被传递给变量，但是
happens if we talk about the cases or
如果我们谈论案件或
the types where we don't have an
我们没有的类型
exhaustive list of values let's
详尽的值列表让我们
and indeed you okay so let me merge this
确实你还好，所以让我合并一下
with and let me define another method I
并让我定义另一种方法
say static and damage again and in this
再说一次静电和损坏，在此
case I let's say I pass the value as a
假设我将值传递为
string and I switch on the method
字符串，我打开方法
parameter and I say if the case is spoon
参数，我说如果是汤匙
the damage is let me define the variable
伤害让我定义变量
again I'm miss defining it earlier so I
再一次我想念它的定义，所以我
define the variable as the local
将变量定义为局部变量
variable as damage and I return this
变量作为损害，我退还这个
variable Y I assign a value 10 to it and
变量YI为其分配值10，并且
I break out of the switch statement so
我打破了switch语句，所以
the other value could be straw and I say
另一个价值可能是稻草，我说
the damage is 11 now again I say break
伤害是11现在我再说一次
out of the switch statement in this case
在这种情况下不在switch语句中
okay so let me insert a switch statement
好吧，让我插入一个switch语句
and okay I am in lining the variable
好吧，我正在衬砌变量
again and now in this case if you see
再一次，现在在这种情况下，如果您看到
IntelliJ IDEA has inserted this line of
IntelliJ IDEA已插入以下行
code it says if I don't pass either of
它说如果我不通过任何一个的代码
these values 0 would be returned but if
这些值0将被返回，但是如果
I delete that particular line now it
我现在删除该特定行
says the switch expression
说开关表达
does not cover all possible input values
不涵盖所有可能的输入值
so when you are returning a value using
因此，当您使用返回值时
switch expressions you must ensure that
切换表达式，您必须确保
the values that you are covering in the
您在其中涵盖的值
switch case labels are exhaustive with
开关盒的标签用
the enums you can define all the
枚举，您可以定义所有
constants but for other values like
常数，但对于其他值，例如
string integer by it short or the other
短整数或其他整数
values which a switch expression accepts
开关表达式接受的值
since the exhaustive list of values
由于值的详尽清单
would not be possible for you to type in
您将无法输入
you would need a default case label so
您将需要一个默认的案例标签，以便
let me insert the default branch here of
让我在这里插入默认分支
course I could modify as required and ok
当然我可以根据需要进行修改，确定
and and let's talk about another format
然后我们来讨论另一种格式
ok so one of the ways of returning
好，所以返回的方式之一
values from switch expressions is to
开关表达式中的值是
just type in the value that we want to
只需输入我们想要的值
return but what if I want to define
返回但是如果我想定义怎么办
let's say a local variable I say number
假设我说一个局部变量
is 100 and then I want to do something
是100，然后我想做点什么
with this number I have some let's say
用这个数字我可以说
some code that manipulates this value I
一些操纵这个值的代码
could also connect to a database or
也可以连接到数据库或
whatever and then I want to return a
什么，然后我想返回一个
value so in this case I could use the
值，因此在这种情况下，我可以使用
break statement and I could return a
中断语句，我可以返回一个
value so this is how I could use a block
值，这就是我可以使用块的方式
of code within a switch branch I could
我可以在switch分支中编写代码
define a local variable and I could use
定义一个局部变量，我可以使用
the break statement to the break keyword
break关键字的break语句
to return a value
返回一个值
I can also
我还可以
yes so let me delete this one and see
是的，所以让我删除这一个，看看
what I could have so as you can see by
我所能拥有的，如你所见
default I could also throw an exception
默认我也可以抛出异常
from a case label so we're talking about
从案件标签中，所以我们正在谈论
so we just talked about using local
所以我们刚才谈到使用本地
variables local variables in switch
开关中的局部变量
branches we talked about using bricks
我们讨论过的使用砖头的分支
statement to return values and this is
返回值的语句，这是
in this is where we are using a a block
在这里我们正在使用一个块
of statement otherwise we could just use
声明，否则我们只能使用
the arrow key to return a value okay so
箭头键可以返回一个值，这样
we have covered pretty much with respect
我们已经涵盖了很多方面
to the switch statements so yes I have a
到switch语句，是的，我有一个
question for you okay
你的问题好吗
okay so this is a quick image to kind of
好吧，这是一种快速的图像
which highlights what is being changed
突出显示正在更改的内容
when I when I go from switch statement
当我离开switch语句时
to switch expressions as you can see the
如您所见，切换表达式
colon which was used in switch
开关中使用的冒号
statements is replaced by an arrow now
语句现在被箭头替换
and instead of using the assignment of a
而不是使用
variable you could just use a value to
您可以使用一个变量来
return we also talked about the comma
返回我们也谈到了逗号
separated multiple case labels your and
分隔多个案例标签，您和
okay so so again I already used the
好的，所以我再次使用了
break statement to return a value so
break语句返回一个值，因此
okay so this one uses another format so
好的，所以这个使用另一种格式
this is an example I guess I missed in
这是我想念的一个例子
my demo so if you take a node it uses a
我的演示，所以如果您使用一个节点，它将使用
colon to start the code and uses break
冒号开始代码并使用break
to return a value
返回一个值
in all the previous examples that I
在前面的所有例子中
showed in my demo it uses an arrow to
在我的演示中显示，它使用箭头
specify the value that you want to
指定您想要的值
return but in the you can also use a
返回，但在您还可以使用
colon followed by the break statement
冒号后面跟着break语句
and the value that you want to return
以及您要返回的值
okay so we've covered the exhaustive
好的，我们已经涵盖了详尽的内容
cases so as I mentioned you would get a
案例，正如我提到的，您会得到一个
compilation error if you try to use
如果您尝试使用编译错误
switch expressions without covering the
切换表达式而不覆盖
exhaustive cases in trying to return a
详尽案例试图返回
value from it okay so yes so this one's
从它的价值好吧，是的，所以这个
for you to answer for the attendees to
让您回答参加者
answer so you would have to tell me
回答，所以你必须告诉我
which one which line of code will enter
输入哪一行代码
to make the code compile is it only one
使代码编译只是一个
or is it line number two okay so also
还是第二行好吗
let me explain so imagine that you have
让我解释一下，想象你有
a class planet and we are talking about
一个阶级的星球，我们正在谈论
a static variable which is private
一个私有的静态变量
static long damage and then I have a
静态的长期伤害，然后我有一个
method which is used and I am switching
使用的方法，我正在切换
on the plastic method parameter which is
在塑性方法参数上
passed to it which doesn't cover all the
传递给它并不能涵盖所有
cases of this enum and the remaining
此枚举和其余的情况
case is plate so we are have only one
情况是盘子，所以我们只有一个
which is remaining so what would be the
剩下的那是什么
right answer if you add line number one
如果添加第一行，则正确答案
will that help this code to compile or
可以帮助此代码进行编译或
if you add line number two will it
如果添加第二行，它将
enable the code to compile or should you
启用代码进行编译还是您应该
add both of them okay just a few minutes
只需几分钟即可将它们都添加
for you to answer the question and then
让您回答问题，然后
I'll move forward to the next slide so
我将前进到下一张幻灯片，以便
perhaps on the count of five I'll move
也许我要数五个
to the next slide
转到下一张幻灯片
to take one tactic to take three
采取一种策略采取三种
they took four hand tactic five and I'll
他们采取了四手战术五，我会
discuss the question at the end of the
在末尾讨论问题
session yes yes the other interesting
会议是是其他有趣
part about the switch expressions is
关于开关表达式的部分是
that it's a preview language feature and
这是一种预览语言功能，
what that essentially means so this is a
这实际上意味着什么，所以这是一个
new concept in Java which was introduced
Java中引入的新概念
in 2018 and what this essentially means
在2018年，这实际上意味着什么
is that it's a new language feature or
是新的语言功能还是
virtual machine feature and it's fully
虚拟机功能，功能全面
specified it's fully implemented yet
指定它已经完全实施
it's not permanent so by having a
它不是永久的，因此
feature as a preview language feature
作为预览语言功能
Oracle gives that feature to try out to
Oracle提供了该功能，可以尝试
the developers and if they have any
开发人员，如果有的话
major problems with the feature then
然后该功能的主要问题
perhaps the feature could be dropped
也许该功能可以删除
altogether or if the problem could be
完全或者如果问题可能是
rectified ma then it the future it would
纠正的马，那么未来它将
be added to the platform with
被添加到平台
modifications and why do you think
修改以及您为什么认为
that's important because Java is almost
这很重要，因为Java几乎
twenty years old now and it's not easy
现在二十岁了，这并不容易
to introduce a new feature whether it's
引入新功能，无论是
a language feature or a platform feature
语言功能或平台功能
if it breaks the existing code because
如果它破坏了现有代码，因为
we are talking about the backward
我们正在谈论落后
compatibility so any new feature which
兼容性，因此任何新功能
is added to the language the platform
被添加到平台语言
should be safe to do so and of course we
这样做应该是安全的，当然我们
are talking about high quality features
在谈论高质量的功能
so the experiment or the the preview
因此，实验或预览
features are not incomplete feature and
功能不是不完整的功能，并且
they are not experimental they are
他们不是实验性的
completely implemented features it's
完全实现的功能
just that Oracle is seeking the
只是Oracle正在寻求
the feedback from developers so that it
开发人员的反馈，以便它
knows yes it's doing that I think before
知道是的，这是我以前想的
it is included in the language okay so
它包含在语言中，所以
here's a tweet from Brian who is the
这是Brian的推文，
chief architect at Oracle so I
Oracle的首席架构师，所以我
deliberately include that in my session
故意在我的会议中加入
just to re-emphasize the fact that yes
只是为了强调这一事实
Oracle is not tagging Java expressions
Oracle未标记Java表达式
as a preview language feature it is
作为预览语言功能
actually seeking feedback from the
实际从
developers so as you can see apart from
开发人员，以便您可以看到
of course the official channels Brian is
当然，布莱恩的官方频道是
looking for the developer feedback on
寻找有关开发人员的反馈
the latest Java future which is switch
最新的Java未来即将到来
expressions and before it exits the
表达式，然后退出
previous status so I asked Brian because
以前的状态，所以我问Brian
I looked around for the last date to
我四处寻找最后的约会
some of the feedback of course there was
当然有一些反馈
no specific date to submit the feedback
没有具体日期提交反馈
but yes if you are thinking of
但是，如果您正在考虑
submitting your feedback now they are
现在提交您的反馈
not accepting it it's done the train has
不接受，火车已经完成了
run it has left the station the platform
运行它已经离开了站台
okay
好的
so here's another link that you can use
所以这是您可以使用的另一个链接
so this is the this page shows the
所以这是此页面显示的
changes to the Java language
更改Java语言
specification and as you can see it was
规格，如您所见
modified just a day back on 20th of May
5月20日一天前修改
2019 and this is the link which you can
2019，这是您可以的链接
use to access this page and it actually
用于访问此页面，实际上
ok I don't have the link here so this is
好的，我这里没有链接，所以这是
just an image and so I'm sorry I
只是一张图片，所以我很抱歉
wouldn't be able to show that in action
不能在行动中证明这一点
to you but if you could access this link
给您，但如果您可以访问此链接
Yasir just type in the address that you
Yasir只需输入您的地址
see here in the address bar and you
在地址栏中看到这里，你
would be able to see how documentation
就能看到文档
on the usage of switch statements
关于switch语句的用法
switch expressions is added to the Java
开关表达式已添加到Java
language specification and I repeat it
语言规范，我重复一遍
was not added yet so it's only now that
还没有被添加，所以直到现在
it has been added and here 14.51
它已经添加，在这里14.51
- you can also see the break with
-您也可以看到与
statement so of course after collecting
声明当然是这样收集后
the feedback from the developers on
来自开发人员的反馈
switch expressions Oracle also included
Oracle还包括开关表达式
another hyphenated keyword - Java
另一个带连字符的关键字-Java
language which is break with so in one
如此与之融为一体的语言
of the examples I would let me go back
我会让我回头的例子
to the example okay so in this case I
这个例子好吧，所以在这种情况下，我
used the break statement to return a
使用break语句返回一个
value but of course I guess this was
值，但我想当然是
sounding a bit confusing to the
听起来有点困惑
developers because we were not used to
开发人员，因为我们不习惯
using a break statement to return a
使用break语句返回一个
value
值
so Oracle has introduced a new keyword
因此，Oracle引入了一个新关键字
which is break with so as you can see
正如您所看到的那样
here the break with statement and moving
在这里与声明的突破和感动
forward you would be a severe Java 12
转发您将是一个严重的Java 12
you can use break statement to return a
您可以使用break语句返回一个
value but moving forward you would be
价值，但向前迈进
able to use break with statement to
能够使用break with语句来
return a value from switch expressions
从开关表达式返回一个值
and Java a Oracle is planning to include
Oracle计划将Java和Java包括在内
a lot of others hyphenated keywords so
许多其他带连字符的关键字
that introduction of new keywords
新关键字的介绍
doesn't break a lot of previous code
不会破坏很多以前的代码
okay so that's a good question for you
好，那对你来说是个好问题
when var was introduced in Java 10 so
在Java 10中引入var时
you have to be honest here so how many
你必须在这里说实话
of you define your variable using the
您使用定义变量
name var right yes oh so that's the
名称var right是的，哦，那是
problem when new keywords are introduced
引入新关键字时出现问题
in the language so using the hyphenated
在语言中，所以使用连字符
keywords would kind of have a lot more
关键字会有更多
oracle would have a lot more
甲骨文会有更多
variable names to add to the language
变量名称以添加到语言
without breaking this existing code okay
不破坏现有代码就可以了
so now let's go to the API changes okay
现在让我们去更改API吧
now again I would refer back to the list
现在我再次回到列表
of the API changes which I showed
我展示的API更改
earlier so again you could click on this
较早，所以您可以再次单击
one and you can actually as I showed
一个，你实际上可以像我展示的那样
earlier you can access all the changes
您可以更早地访问所有更改
which are included in the in Java 12 and
它们包含在Java 12和
I did not include any specific examples
我没有提供任何具体示例
on purpose for this because it's easy to
故意这样做是因为它很容易
just kind of sit back and watch through
只是坐下来观察
the example codes and I would really
示例代码，我真的会
like you to first of all find out what
像你这样首先找出
are the modifications or the additions
是修改还是添加
or even the removals in Java to well and
甚至对Java的删除也是如此
I don't know please excuse this window
我不知道请问这个窗口
sorry and then try out the new language
抱歉，然后尝试新的语言
editions yourself okay so let's go back
可以自己编辑，让我们回去
to okay so so Java 12 has also added a
可以，所以Java 12还添加了一个
new API which is a new package java.lang
新的API，它是一个新的包java.lang
dot constant and all of these classes
点常量和所有这些类
now include a resolve constant
现在包括一个解析常数
description method
描述方法
deac for short and again I have not
短短的耳聋，再一次我没有
included a code deliberately on on
包括故意在
purpose for this one JDK 12 also
JDK 12的目的也是
supports a lot of new characters we are
支持很多新角色
talking about chess symbols here we're
在这里谈论国际象棋符号
talking about my own numerous
谈论我自己的无数
which is an interesting base 20 new
这是一个有趣的基础20新
medical system and a lot of other
医疗系统和许多其他
languages as well okay so now we are
语言也好，所以现在我们是
talking about the JVM changes so I'll
谈论JVM的变化，所以我将
quickly talk about the Neo experiment
快速谈论Neo实验
experimental garbage collector which is
实验性垃圾收集器
the shenandoah this garbage collector is
shenandoah这个垃圾收集器是
proposed and developed by engineers at
由工程师在
Red Hat
红色的帽子
it promises significantly low pauses
它保证了极低的停顿
it's a region based garbage collector
这是一个基于区域的垃圾收集器
which collects garbage in parallel and
并行收集垃圾
concurrent manner it is interesting to
并发方式很有趣
note that the pause times are
请注意，暂停时间为
independent of applications live data
独立于应用程序实时数据
which is unlike the previous garbage
与之前的垃圾不同
collectors Java head and with the
收藏家的Java头和
hardware engineering and lower cost
硬件工程和较低的成本
servers have more memory and processing
服务器有更多的内存和处理能力
power than ever before and modern
力量比以往任何时候都现代
applications are increasingly demanding
应用程序要求越来越高
lower post times with service level
通过服务水平缩短发布时间
agreement applications that guarantee
协议申请保证
response times of 10 to 500 milliseconds
响应时间为10到500毫秒
so to meet the low end of the range
所以要满足范围的低端
shenandoah GC is able to meet that lower
shenandoah GC能够满足较低的要求
end and it uses algorithms that enables
最后，它使用的算法可以
programs to execute with the given
给定要执行的程序
memory the other point is that it can
记忆的另一点是，它可以
keep the pause times low as low as below
保持暂停时间低至如下
10 milliseconds if you talk
如果您说10毫秒
the other garbage collectors that's not
其他不是的垃圾收集器
attainable with let's say a java
用Java可以达到
application that use 200 gb of memory
使用200 GB内存的应用程序
and it isn't possible with the compact
紧凑型是不可能的
compacting algorithms which would exceed
压缩算法将超过
the limit of 10 milliseconds because
限制为10毫秒，因为
even for compacting 10% of this memory
即使压缩10％的内存
that would exceed the timings Shenandoah
那将超过雪兰多的时间
uses an in-court algorithm that compacts
使用压缩的庭内算法
the memory concurrently while the Java
Java并发存储
threads are running and in this case
线程正在运行，在这种情况下
objects are moved during concurrent GC
对象在并发GC期间移动
cycle and all its references immediately
循环及其所有参考
access the new a copy the other
访问新的副本其他
modifications in GC space is a bot able
修改GC空间是一个机器人能够
mixed collections for garbage first GC g
垃圾优先GC的混合收集
1 GC as we call it so what happens when
我们称之为1 GC，那么什么时候发生
the garbage first
垃圾第一
GC tries to collect the garbage from the
GC尝试从
young regions so the young regions are
年轻地区，所以年轻地区是
the ones which are where the objects are
那些是对象所在的地方
frequently used and discarded and we
经常使用和丢弃，我们
have the old regions where we have
有我们有的旧地区
objects which have lived quite a long
寿命很长的物体
time much longer than the young
时间比年轻人长得多
collections so what happens when the g1
集合，那么当g1会发生什么
GC runs out of memory it first tries to
GC首先用尽了内存不足
free the young college young spaces and
释放年轻的大学青年空间，并
then if it cannot keep up with the
那么如果它跟不上
allocation by cleaning up the young
通过清理年轻人来分配
collection then it goes for cleaning up
收集然后清理
a mixed collection which includes the
混合集合，其中包括
old and the new generation but in that
老一辈和新一代，但在那
case what happens if I want to abort the
如果我想中止该怎么办
collection before JDK 12 that was not
JDK 12之前的集合不是
possible but with JDK 12 it is possible
可能，但是使用JDK 12可以
for me to abort a mixed collection for
我中止了
the
的
even garbage collector of course when I
当然，即使是垃圾收集器
say I can abort a collection I am
说我可以中止我的收藏
cutting down on the time so what happens
减少时间，那么会发生什么
most a lot of applications are now
现在大多数应用程序
running in container spaces so what
在容器空间中运行
happens if you have multiple
如果您有多个会发生
applications or you have multiple gbm's
应用程序，或者您有多个gbm
and they are using the memory which the
他们正在使用的内存
one which has been assigned to them but
一个已经分配给他们，但
they are not using it in that case the
在这种情况下，他们不使用它
the organization running those
运行这些的组织
applications would have to pay more for
申请将不得不为
running the applications because we are
运行应用程序，因为我们
talking about paying for the resources
谈论支付资源
again if if an application is using
如果应用程序正在使用
resources which are not being used such
未被使用的资源
as memory then it's it's something that
作为记忆，那就是
needs to be corrected so with Java 12
需要更正，因此使用Java 12
the G 1 garbage collector can promptly
G 1垃圾收集器可以迅速
return the unused committed memory from
返回未使用的已提交内存
a noose committed memory because there
绞索承诺的记忆，因为那里
are only two times when the garbage
当垃圾只有两次
collector returns the memory so the one
收集器返回内存，所以一个
is the full GC which is the full garbage
是完整的GC，是完整的垃圾
collection and that only happens that
收集，只有这样
really happens so G one would do all
真的发生了，所以一个人会全力以赴
that it can to avoid a full garbage
可以避免完全的垃圾
collection it would try to free up the
收集它会尝试释放
young spaces and only if it doesn't
年轻的空间，如果没有
manage to to manage to allocate more
设法分配更多
objects then it would go for a full the
对象，那么它将去完整的
bitch collection and that's one time
母狗收集，那是一次
when a garbage collector would return
垃圾收集器何时返回
the unused committed memory to the host
未使用的提交给主机的内存
but with JDK twelve you could terminate
但是使用JDK 12，您可以终止
to return the uncommitted memory at
返回未提交的内存
particular times or events okay so
特定的时间或事件可以
so that's the last slide and I would
这是最后一张幻灯片，我会
like to leave you with one of the tweets
喜欢留下一条推文
which I received for for one of the
我收到的其中一个
polls that I mentioned initially so it
我最初提到的民意调查
says the upgrade to Java 9 seemed like a
说升级到Java 9似乎是
huge step until it was clear that if I
迈出了一大步，直到很明显，如果我
didn't really need jigsaw I could pretty
我真的不需要拼图，我可以漂亮
much ignore it from Java 9 to 12 isn't a
从Java 9到12忽略它不是一个
big deal as moving from 7 to 8 so what
从7变到8的确很重要
that essentially means that we could be
这实质上意味着我们可以
thinking about steps ABC to migrate to a
考虑步骤ABC迁移到
certain level but we could also realize
一定水平，但我们也可以意识到
that we might not need those steps to
我们可能不需要这些步骤
move to a newer versions so as as Java
迁移到新版本，例如Java
developers architects managers we need
我们需要的开发人员，建筑师，经理
to know what are the options which exist
知道存在哪些选择
for when we are updating our technology
当我们更新技术时
wardrobes because to make good decisions
衣柜，因为要做出正确的决定
we must be aware about the choices that
我们必须意识到选择
we have and it's only from a good tool
我们有，而且只有一个好的工具
of choice that we can make a good
我们可以做出好的选择
decision
决定
so my advice if you are thinking about
所以我的建议，如果您正在考虑
moving to Java 12 I would suggest that
转向Java 12我建议
even if you are so Java 12 is a
即使您是Java 12，
short-term support release and since we
短期支持发布，以及由于我们
had Java 11 which was a long-term
Java 11是长期的
support release just six months back I
支持发布仅六个月前
would advise you to move to Java 11 but
会建议您转到Java 11，但是
as developers I would like you to use a
作为开发人员，我希望您使用
platforms like IntelliJ IDEA where you
像IntelliJ IDEA这样的平台
could you could compile your code and
你可以编译代码并
run it against multiple versions and see
针对多个版本运行它，看看
where the problem lies if you let's say
如果您说问题出在哪里
if you're moving your code to Java 11
如果要将代码迁移到Java 11
and if you try if you plan to move it to
如果您尝试将其移至
a later version sometime later it's good
一个更高版本的某个时间以后会很好
to test your existing code against the
来测试现有代码
newer versions
较新的版本
because Java from Java 9 Oracle has
因为Java 9 Oracle中的Java具有
started taking off the deprecated API
开始删除已弃用的API
more seriously and they are not just
更严重的是，他们不只是
letting you go with the compilation
让您进行编译
errors they are removing the api's so
错误，他们正在删除API的
it's a it's a small migration I would
这是一个很小的迁移，我会
say to be on Java 11 but test your code
说要在Java 11上运行，但要测试您的代码
on Java 12 so that you know that now
在Java 12上，这样您现在就知道了
there are no major showstoppers or
没有主要的热门节目或
roadblocks so that when you move to a
障碍，以便当您移至
newer version you get to see a lot of
较新的版本，您会看到很多
problems thank you so much and I'm good
问题非常感谢你，我很好
to take the questions now
现在就提问
thanks so much mala that was great and
非常感谢，很棒，
we have had a bunch of questions I
我有很多问题
answered a few of them on the backend
在后端回答了其中的一些
and from what I understood particularly
根据我的特别理解
around switch expressions there was one
开关表达式周围有一个
question which I was kind of interested
我有点感兴趣的问题
to know what the answer was the question
知道答案是什么
was can we join the default section with
是我们可以加入默认部分吗
another case section if the return
如果返回其他案例部分
values are the same or does default
值相同或默认
always have to be separate yes I guess
总是必须分开是的，我猜
it always has to be separate we can't
它总是必须分开我们不能
have that I would really enjoy it my
有我真的会喜欢我的
friend yeah Oh because it's not case
朋友，是啊，因为不是这样
doesn't start with case right right
不是从大小写正确开始
right so it only has D point so I don't
对，所以只有D点，所以我没有
think that's possible I agree I think
认为有可能我同意
you could try it but I think it's you're
你可以试试看，但我想是你
going to get some sort of compiler error
会得到某种编译器错误
all right
好吧
made yeah so if your default bare well
是的，所以如果您的默认设置很好
actually so try that try turning the
实际上，所以尝试尝试将
default fare to 11 and see what IntelliJ
默认票价为11，看看IntelliJ是什么
IDEA suggests because I think it would
IDEA建议，因为我认为这样会
want you to delete straw and cup because
想要您删除吸管和杯子，因为
that's dealt with by by the default
默认情况下处理
there you go see
你去那里看看
in case it says delete redundant switch
万一说删除冗余开关
branch
科
okay so it has okay so you cannot
好的，所以它可以，所以你不能
actually have the default case with
实际具有默认情况
other cases so in this case IntelliJ
其他情况下，在这种情况下，IntelliJ
IDEA stated that okay so because you are
IDEA表示，好的，因为您是
using the same a return value for the
使用相同的返回值
default branch and for the other labels
默认分支和其他标签
so those labels were redundant and it
所以那些标签是多余的，它
just removed those yeah that makes sense
刚刚删除了那些有意义的
okay so let me see also there was so at
好吧，让我看看那里也是如此
your slide where you asked the question
您问问题的幻灯片
about which code would fix the problem
关于哪个代码可以解决问题
right we had a number of now as you'd
对，我们有很多现在
expect we'd have a number we had a
希望我们有一个号码，我们有一个
number of different answers to that why
为什么会有不同的答案
was it so yes right so there was a
是吗，是的，所以有一个
possibility of either adding a another
添加另一个的可能性
enum value or adding the default value
枚举值或添加默认值
so we had some people saying we need the
所以有人说我们需要
default some people saying both some
默认有人说两个
people saying either yes some people
人们说有些人
saying either all right so the correct
说好吧，所以正确
answer is either because we are talking
答案是因为我们在说话
about switch expressions which are
关于开关表达式
returning a value and because as I
返回一个值，因为像我
mentioned the plate is the only in
提到板是唯一的
evaluating from the case labels so
从案例标签进行评估，以便
either you could add line number 1 or
您可以添加行号1或
line number 2 of course if you would add
第2行，当然，如果您要添加
both of them it would be correct as well
他们两个都是正确的
but the answer was which one of them
但答案是其中之一
should you and so yes I think the answer
应该吗，是的，我想答案
would be one or two or both ok that's
会是一两个还是两个都可以
great
大
there was also some confusion around the
周围也有些混乱
break and break width so as far as I
就我而言，打破和打破宽度
understand it because people were sort
了解它是因为人们很友善
of saying how can you use break to
说如何使用break来
return values and break to jump to
返回值并中断跳转
labels and how does it work with the
标签以及它如何与
backwards compatibility so I believe
向后兼容，所以我相信
what you're saying is that what they
你的意思是说他们
will do from Java 13 onwards
从Java 13开始
you won't use break you use break with
你不会用break你会用break
is that right all right right so as I
是这样吗，就像我一样
mentioned so that's a preview language
提到所以这是一种预览语言
feature and the oracle was trying to
功能和甲骨文试图
collect the feedback and a lot of
收集反馈和很多
developers suggested the same thing so
开发人员提出了同样的建议
there was a lot of confusion when to use
使用时有很多困惑
break without a value and when to use
没有价值的突破以及何时使用
break with a value so they have modified
打破一个值，所以他们已经修改
the switch expression so instead of
开关表达式，所以代替
using the break statement with a value
使用带有值的break语句
to return a value they are they would be
返回一个值，他们将是
now using break width which is break -
现在使用的中断宽度是break-
with but that would apply from the next
与，但将适用于下一个
version or yes the next version but not
版本或是下一个版本，但不是
this version so with Java - well you can
Java的这个版本，所以您可以
still use break and then the value to
仍然使用break然后将值
return a value from a this is where the
从那里返回一个值
new release cadence gets a little bit
新发行节奏有一点点
confusing right because and the fact
混淆的权利，因为和事实
that we have preview features because as
我们具有预览功能，因为
you said right at the beginning preview
您是在开始预览时说的
features are kind of malleable they are
特征是可塑的
likely to change so we shouldn't really
可能会改变，所以我们不应该真的
have been using Java 12 with preview
一直在使用Java 12进行预览
features in production because there's a
生产中的功能，因为有一个
good chance that switch expressions will
开关表达式将很有可能
change going forward all right right
改变前进没事吧
you're right because that's as good as
你是对的，因为那和
saying that they have a beta feature
说他们有测试版功能
which they are giving out to the
他们正在分发给
developers and as with every beta
开发人员以及每个beta
feature that we know yes we have a
我们知道的功能是，我们有一个
possibility of change there so it's good
在那里改变的可能性很好
for the developers to try it out to help
给开发人员尝试帮助
shape how they would like their Java to
决定他们希望Java如何
be but of course there there is a risk
会存在，但当然存在风险
factor there because if we are using
在那里，因为如果我们使用
introduction then we would have to
介绍，那么我们将不得不
change it yeah exactly and I think
完全改变它，我认为
that's an important thing to notice we
重要的是要注意我们
should be using the preview features to
应该使用预览功能
as you say help shape the language give
当你说帮助塑造语言给
feedback and say what's working and
反馈并说出什么在起作用，
what's not right because it's easy to to
什么不对，因为很容易
crib about some features it's easy to
婴儿床一些功能很容易
say Oh JA tha is not doing let's say
说哦JA tha没做让我们说
things a B or C but it's important to
是B还是C，但重要的是
participate and give your feedback and
参与并提供您的反馈意见，
by just using it so so we're not Oracle
只使用它，所以我们不是Oracle
is not asking for a lot of input
并不需要很多投入
they're not asking for every person to
他们并没有要求每个人都
go and contribute to the API or
去贡献API或
something but by just testing it out
只是通过测试而已
developers can help shape Java as they
开发人员可以帮助他们塑造Java
want to be yeah and so there's a related
想成为，所以有一个相关的
question here is there a way to prohibit
问题在这里，有一种方法可以禁止
is there a way to prohibit preview
有没有办法禁止预览
features in build configuration eg by
构建配置中的功能，例如通过
supplying arguments to the compiler and
向编译器提供参数
the answer is actually by default you
答案实际上是默认情况下的
don't get preview features right they're
没有正确的预览功能
not learned on like default all right
没有像默认一样学习
right but the experimental features and
对，但实验功能和
the preview features they are turned off
预览功能已关闭
by default and to use them you have to
默认情况下，要使用它们，您必须
turn them on by supplying the the
通过提供将它们打开
relevant command-line arguments and of
相关的命令行参数和
course when we configure it in IntelliJ
当然，当我们在IntelliJ中配置它时
IDEA that adds it to the configuration
将其添加到配置的IDEA
adds it to the tools the compilation
将其添加到编译工具中
process right I have a question here
处理正确，我在这里有一个问题
will Java 12 work with spring boot to
Java 12是否可以与Spring Boot一起使用
spring go to framework and with spring 5
春天进入框架并在 spring 5
plus framework and I don't have an
加框架，我没有
answer day so perhaps we could bring
回答一天，也许我们可以带
Josh on that one I was using Java 12
Josh关于那个我正在使用Java 12的文章
weather with a few bits and pieces it
一点点的天气
seems to just work seamlessly but I
似乎只是无缝地工作，但我
think again like you said earlier like
再想一次，就像你刚才说的那样
going from 11 to 12 is fairly painless
从11到12相当轻松
but going from say 8 to 12 might be a
但是从8到12可能是一个
bit of a bigger jump as far as I'm aware
据我所知，跳远了一点
all the common libraries appear to work
所有常见的库似乎都可以工作
with Java 12 but we can find out and
使用Java 12，但我们可以找出并
what I'll do actually were the questions
我要做的实际上是问题
we can't fully answer and what we'll do
我们无法完全回答，我们会做什么
is we'll make a note of them and then we
是我们会记下它们，然后我们
can add them to a blog post at the end
可以在最后将它们添加到博客文章中
where when we post the recording of the
当我们发布记录的地方
webinar we can also post answers to the
网络研讨会中，我们还可以发布答案
questions we couldn't answer all right
我们无法回答的问题
right that would be great yeah and
是的，那太好了，
there's another question about did you
还有一个关于你的问题
mention a constable type earlier on come
提早提到一个常量类型
again did I mention constable type I
我再一次提到了I型
think it's something it's an input of
认为这是它的输入
project amber I think but I don't
我认为是琥珀色但我不喜欢
remember you mentioning it might have
记得你提到它可能有
been one of
曾经是
the in one of the sorry let me find it
抱歉之一让我找到它
sorry and just trying to scroll past
对不起，只是试图滚动过去
other questions and the string changes
其他问题和字符串更改
there was some mention when you looked
当你看时有提及
at that when you look to the string API
当您查看字符串API时
changes in the first section of
第一部分的变化
constable type okay
常量类型好
yes oh there we go yeah yes so that's a
是的，哦，我们走了，是的，那是一个
neocon interface that we have in
我们拥有的neocon界面
java.lang package and we also have
java.lang包，我们也有
another interface which is constant de
另一个接口是常数de
SE and I would really encourage the
SE和我真的会鼓励
person who was asking to go through the
要求通过的人
documentation because what I see with a
文档，因为我看到的是
lot of developers is that they don't
很多开发人员是他们不
read through a lot of documentation and
通读大量文档，然后
then they miss a lot of points so yes
然后他们错过了很多点，所以是的
they can access this URL here and they
他们可以在此处访问此网址，
could just go through it I will also
可以通过它我也会
post that URL in the blog post when we
当我们在博客文章中发布该网址时
have the recording later on because I
以后有录音，因为我
had people asking for that URL and okay
有人问这个网址，好吧
and there was another question around
周围还有另一个问题
they were cuz there was confusion around
他们是因为周围有混乱
what a mixed collections and what's the
什么是混合收藏，什么是
meaning of a portable around garbage
随身携带垃圾的意思
collection and I think again maybe what
收集，我再想一想
we'll do is we'll post further
我们要做的就是进一步发布
information about some the garbage
有关一些垃圾的信息
collection changes the specific changes
集合更改的具体更改
you went through and then if people want
你经历了，然后如果人们想要
to find out things in more detail
找出更多细节
they could perhaps follow those links
他们也许可以跟随这些链接
and and read that documentation make
然后阅读该文档
sense yeah okay great and I believe
感觉很好，很好，我相信
we've answered all of the questions
我们已经回答了所有问题
which are in the the webinar window and
在网络研讨会窗口中
thank you everyone for being such a
谢谢大家这么好
fantastic engaging audience you were
您曾经是极富吸引力的观众
very active in the questions as I said
我说的问题非常活跃
what we'll do is we will post a blog
我们要做的是发布博客
post which includes a video which open
包含打开视频的帖子
please a link to the video when this
请在此链接到视频
recording is available we will answer
有录音，我们会回答
any unanswered questions which also
任何未回答的问题
means that if you didn't get a chance to
表示如果您没有机会
answer to ask your question right now
立即回答您的问题
please feel free to ping us over Twitter
请随时通过Twitter对我们进行ping操作
or or perhaps send us an email so on
或者也许给我们发电子邮件等等
Twitter do you
Twitter你
you have our handles on the first slide
你在第一张幻灯片上有我们的手柄
our Twitter handles on there I don't
我们的Twitter处理我不
think so so it's email a gutter and
这么想，所以给它发了一封电子邮件，
Trisha underscore G on Twitter so feel
Trisha在Twitter上强调了G，所以感觉
free to ask us questions even after the
即使在
webinar and we can we can answer those
网络研讨会，我们可以回答这些问题
in the blog post and and thank you very
在博客文章中，非常感谢
much you've been a fantastic audience
你真是一个了不起的听众
and thank you matter what a really great
谢谢你，这真的很棒
presentation about what's new in JDK 12
JDK 12新增功能的演示文稿
you
您